Guide to the Center for Language Study, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Center for Language Study, Yale University, records
1965-1999
RU 928
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
The records consist of a 1979 report to the provost and annual reports of the Yale Language Laboratory.
Yale University. Center for Language Study
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-D (YRG 3-D), Records documenting academic support functions at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Center for Language Study, 2003.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
The Center for Language Study (CLIS) was established at Yale in 1999. The Language Laboratory, which had been administratively under Information Technology Services, became part of the center in the same year.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of a 1979 report to the provost and annual reports of the Yale Language Laboratory.
Language and languages -- Study and teaching; Language laboratories; Annual reports; Yale University. Center for Language Study; Yale University. Information Technology Services
- Reports, 1965-1999; Accession 2003-A-099
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2034
  - Provost Report, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Annual reports
    - 1965-1981 (Box 1)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 1)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1)
    - 1985-1990 (Box 1)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 1)